HARRISON MAINDONALD

Personality Highlights

- Self-motivated and mostly self-taught
- Motivated by solving problems
- Fast learner
- Independent worker

Skills

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- React/Angular/Polymer
- C#
- Golang
- Java
- MySQL, Firebase
- Mobile Development

Contact Details

- <u>harry.maindonald@hotmail</u>
 <u>.com</u>
- https://harrymaindonald.githu
 b.io/portfolio/
- https://github.com/harrymaind
 onald/portfolio
- 0211448087

Summary

Junior Web Developer specializing in front end and full stack web development. Experienced with all stages of the development life cycle for dynamic web projects.

Strong desire to always be learning and improving myself. I am a faster learner which helps me quickly integrate into a team environment.

Education

Bachelor of Digital Technologies

Majoring in Software and Web Development Manukau Institute of Technology, 2017 – 2019

- Top student award for Project Management, Level 6
- A+ grade for final Industry Project

Diploma of Information and Communication Technologies

Manukau Institute of Technology, 2012 - 2014

NCEA Level 1,2 & 3

Sacred Heart College, 2006 - 2011

Level 1 & 2 Endorsed with Merit

Professional Experience

Front end Developer Intern

Unify Digital, July 2018 – December 2018
Created a progressive web application for the existing Unify
Digital staff, to assist in capturing and displaying JavaScript
errors as they occur within their products. Learnt a JavaScript
library to make this – Polymer, which utilizes web components.

Full Stack Developer

FlocknSave Limited, June 2018 – Present

Maintaining their current Web App – FlocknSave, which runs with Golang. Most of my work for FlocknSave has involved improving the state of the UI which uses Golang templating and SASS CSS.

Stockroom Supervisor

Puma NZ, March 2019 - Present

Leading a team of 4, I maintain the operational flow of Puma's stockroom, ensuring all deliveries are processed, stockroom organization is kept to standards, and incoming stock is received into the database. This involves using the company's software to maintain their stock database and using data entry to deal with stock variances.